May 15, 2023. We have the invocation from Pastor and we got to say pastor this time for our business first Christian Church
Please bow! Father God will love you
Thankful To be in such a great community
I thank Your Word tells us pray For The Prosperity of Our Community
for our neighbors and For Our Businesses. And God, we do that right now
We pray
For the moment that you've given us and we ask That, God your Word also says to pray for our leaders. And so
We do it!
Our local elected officials who are making decisions in continuing this great momentum
So guys
Prayed You Would Bless Everything Happens Tonight Give Wisdom & discernment
And allow us to keep growing and Keep Doing Good Things
Overall Father, we pray that We Would Be More Like Jesus
It Says Name With Pray Amen
And Connecting Studies as well As Working With Tetic Tech to Discuss
Seminamic Whistings of JREA SEMOTATION studies
Again, it was obviously a very active month relating in the 68k
$23090 and voice However that's Well Within Our Budget
I'm this particular fiscal year
And if You approve that item, we Will Still Have Remaining
340k and 737
We're just your expectations of the remainder Of The fiscal Year as far As What
WE GOT
Should Be Very Light I Know
Had That
This conversation a couple A times
Because Last When
We Had To Actually Included Our Town Hall
It was a great deal of activity
Obviously immediately, leading up to That
And then Right After The
A couple Of Embois Just Coming In
This Being the One For Me You Have Achieved in Large Wind
Which Was All The Filings that Came Through March
Really Now With Into THE Year
we Don't have lot Backtivity and Fire
Again I Think Until September
So this Money with Im Budget Roll Over
If There
Let's Say What Happens What Those Dollars
So My Expectation When That Ines Up in the Carry Over
We Did Is Rebutiated
so Yeah, we Pick It up and Re-budget it Next Year
And Then What Are WE BUDGING For
what arewebudging next year?
I'm Sorry.
This is Available To Me But i Can't Remember
$50000
Same as The Sure
Thats How As Asked him He's Going to Be
this Thing
You Know
Last Year Didn'T Know
From A Much Of Us
So There'e Expectations that
Were going SeeThe same amount of Cost
Next Year
as well. I mean,
there's no real way to know but
likely
we have a game
that is really the only
what filing
they're going
made so it depends on
how long first
cracks this out
through GRE
or in FIRG
make some determinations
and asking
GERDI
into
whole team
finally
had from DCC
start
court
then could be more
activity
I'm going to say odds are pretty good, but still be within that budget.
So is there any precedent this suggests
if you're in the end of it or can't go on forever?
Not really!
The determination would have been about 25-25
and less Jürgen came out
and did not want to use your license 25
but that's for the extension, which I can imagine they would.
If you're in a fair court making determination?
They had though extended out of pass-out right!
So if we didn't do it before,
then some other performing all studies
will require them
should have those wrapped up
while having their way back through
and their final application to do March or May 31st.
At this time, yeah it's still there!
So what kind of activity have we already for seen?
Or are you ready seeing in our April I mean
because were improving from March right
Yeah i think the direct feedback will look
Think We had a potential invoice at 1k400
Yeah we'd be dead with you.
He tried to send those F4s from Tyler and I can't keep an eye on them
so if they have a Park Stinson,
We know what the ARM is saying coming in there
It's still not some outstanding stuff
Nothing this, it seems like he said
Oh my commotion improved
Second
Okay, now discussion of options for solid waste tipping fees
For the transfer situation
Tyler and Kevin
So we have Will Dan coming in next Monday
We're excited to talk about this speed plus
Well, Dan Jackson is a gentleman
That did last so i don't know how many different fees
Because of not great fee
Could typically be answering other questions
Packet as always that report
In our tonage if you brought it
The lost two years
It's just like saying right now
Oh, okay
We looked for any land
Another conversation today
Looking and talking
Really expressing that desire
Just about every one in the area
I don't really get a conversation with DQ
They said you can expect two to three years
Which is good
That we were actually concerned
The Q did was basically gave us some encouragement
Has new contract put it down
And expenses
We just started this month so
Do you anticipate put a dinner?
I think it'll decrease, but still
Have any of them ever given anything on what i talked about
Ripping materials
Can we reach out to DQ or something outside of the facility
Let's back and submit some improvement here
Maybe a transfer situation don't accept
Singles anymore
One of the things we talked about last time
When you talk to me
We discussed in our last meeting
And when I was talking
About doing some different pricing
If i don't know if he heard that
So, what are going on with the same as
We've done but then do a commercial rate
It's higher and they're
Out-of-towns already high
But it is not high enough
We're still losing money on all of them
Right, right
But that's what we'll talk about next week
And give him a little bit more
That could be the weather too
So does anyone take it somewhere else
I mean i would assume they are
There is alot more risk involved than that
You know i said trade up over town
Even in my neighborhood
People didn't get new roads
They just wanted to run
Wanted money, we had a different library
And that's not the next one
But I'm going work with dirty trade
So i don't know where they took it
We did talk about last week
Which part?
Raising rates
The guy from the old days coming
Next weekend
We think we'll raise the rates for that
Added down to high enough
Maybe even discourage
Every second you talk about whatever
That's what i'm talking about
What do y'all come up with
You look at those two local businesses
Got dumped there, will bring a box from out of town
To dump in
Town they can business
So if someone brings
The box from commerce
To my am a they charge them out of town
Or someone picks up the boxes at local business
That don't
Do trash service here but has electric service
They still are going to have it down right
Even though their paying utility customer
So there's alot
Things that really needy be discussed
You know, numbers in report
What?
You can bring your attention
Like call them i the fiscal year
Last years of this time
We spent 510,000
This was a day
To pay for over a million
We've absolutely doubled that cost
500k
In transfer station
For transfer station
We've only brought in 575
Which is why that track was last year's cost
So the fees were set to recover our costs
And we're a cost of half million at this time
A fee will cover it
But now its 1,000 and half million
That´s what i got
Well ,we did have contract or come from out estate
In coming into my amica
It would be cheaper
Not for attention
And contract for the Northgate
I know Bill or County
They're a $1 higher than an odd town
Right here across north of everybody
You don't have any income
There are more than about...
...or 60 dollars at that time
But they also charge 75
Roofing materials
That's in charge 90 per yard
We don't need a free
I just ran off their website
Wow
There are lot of levers
You can do different things with the sea
But obviously if you have an impact
They're having a bad business
Maybe in effect of the extension
We got to cover our costs
Well it's happening back now
Like 5,000 dollars
That is coming up somewhere
So we just came into the sea
Yeah so come next week and talk about how
The breakdown of fees
And I don't mean they can give you that one
In 3 dollars in a day or three cents
Thanking these for having us to address
If any other days
To be able with them
That also goes into...
Process of fuel size
I mean that's a good to transfer station
And get the loader onto directs and all
The last thing we talked about is
Closing
Transferstation in June
To repair two columns
So you can clear it out
Watch for the floor off
We're at their column set
What do they have?
They don't really want people
I personally don't like that
If people are welding in there
Oh great but if we can
Take it outside and what do they have?
We'll go up here
Around the earth
What about their out-flat wolf
They're also an entire need of repairs
But its kind
And how many times would you put a bit of a good given
Didnít get any bits last two time
So i guess to work with them
To, you know in the right city we put into money
to build a new facility
Or even move that money towards putting it on landfill
That do want us spend three or four hundred thousand dollars
Take out of our money
But can way away through years
If anything about what they have built
I mean i was never going
I'm pretty impressed
It's lasted long personally
And probably didn't get any repair
And the big fire didn't they?
Can i have us what are you thinking about that outside of all
We canít risk our peopleís lives for something like that
So, yeah so interesting
The life safety obviously is well we want to do men
I think will be able get your own better information
Next week and then weíll dance here
If it starts giving me more budget aspect
What rates would there wwe could deal with
And then we can't do it with different types of outcomes
You want to face what you got
We wanted try and get a land fill
Obviously the land fill is great solution
Ultimately could have many benefits
To, in time iíll reach the city of Miami
But obviously bigger project
In another big price tag
but
When need talk about that
Stop pouring money into this one
But we know what you got to do these life safety issues
Again next week i think for having easier time
Give me the data that I really kind of thinking about
What can y'know if they want it?
We look forward with material and their x-savvy
If every scene is on its like, they have them
It's crappy arts or anything but finding out how much her hand seems
Any questions from your collarer Kevin
Thankyou
Thanks Kevin
Another new business of any which is written
Supposed to this agenda
11 staff report
12 trustee community house books
13. This meeting will be continued from council chambers
Reconvening the staff room for purpose executive session
At completion i donít 15
To The Regger city council